Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
- Box: 36, Folder: 3 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.432 (1951:July 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.434 (1951:Aug. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.435 (1951:Aug. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.436 (1951:Aug. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.438 (1951:Aug. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.439 (1951:Aug. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.440 (1951:Sep. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.443 (1951:Sep. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.444 (1951:Sep. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.446 (1951:Sep. 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.448 (1951:Oct. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.451 (1951:Oct. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.452 (1951:Oct. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.453 (1951:Oct. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.454 (1951:Nov. 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.455 (1951:Nov. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.469 (1952:Jan. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.472 (1952:Feb. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.473 (1952:Feb. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.474 (1952:Feb. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.475 (1952:Mar. 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.476 (1952:Mar. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.477 (1952:Mar. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.478 (1952:Mar. 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.479 (1952:Apr. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.480 (1952:Apr. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.481 (1952:Apr. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.482 (1952:Apr. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.483 (1952:May 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.484 (1952:May 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.485 (1952:May 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.487 (1952:May 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.488 (1952:May 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.489 (1952:June 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.490 (1952:June 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.491 (1952:June 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.492 (1952:June 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.? (1952:July 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.493 (1952:July 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.476 (1952:Sep. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.477 (1952:Sep. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.478 (1952:Oct. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.480 (1952:Oct. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.481 (1952:Oct. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.482 (1952:Nov. 7). Item is in English.
- Box: 36, Folder: 4 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.295 (1948:Dec. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.406 (1951:Feb. 9/16). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.407 (1951:Feb. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.408 (1951:Mar. 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.409 (1951:Mar. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.410 (1951:Mar. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.412 (1951:Mar. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.413 (1951:Apr. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.414 (1951:Apr. 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.415 (1951:Apr. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.417 (1951:Apr. 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.418 (1951:May 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.419 (1951:May 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.420 (1951:May 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.421 (1951:May 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.422 (1951:May 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.423 (1951:May 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.445 (1951:Sep. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.457 (1951:Nov. 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.458 (1951:Nov. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.459 (1951:Nov. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.460 (1951:Nov. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.462 (1951:Dec. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.463 (1951:Dec. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.464 (1951:Dec. 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.465 (1952:Jan. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.466 (1952:Jan. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.467 (1952:Jan. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.470 (1952:Feb. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.471 (1952:Feb. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.483 (1952:Nov. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.484 (1952:Nov. 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.485 (1952:Nov. 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.486 (1952:Dec. 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.487 (1952:Dec. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.490 (1952:Dec. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.113 (1963:May 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.114 (1963:May 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America. no.116 (1963:June 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Memo to Management, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Frank Rising. MM-59 (1950:Nov. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 41: "Do" Rating Code Symbols, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Automobile and Automotive Parts Manufacturers. AAPM Bulletin no.1792- 2 (1951:June 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: The International Convention of the Men's and Boys' Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.384 (1950:Sep. 8). Item is in English.
- Box: 36, Folder: 5 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.387 (1950:Sep. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.388 (1950:Oct. 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.389 (1950:Oct. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.390 (1950:Nov. 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.392 (1950:Nov. 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.393 (1950:Nov. 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.394 (1950:Nov. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.395 (1950:Dec. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.396 (1950:Dec. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.397 (1950:Dec. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.398 (1950:Dec. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.399 (1950:Dec. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.400 (1951:Jan. 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.401 (1951:Jan. 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.402 (1951:Jan. 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.403 (1951:Jan. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.404 (1951:Jan. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.405 (1951:Feb. 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.385 (1950:Sep. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Associated News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By Clothing Manufactures Association of The United States of America. no.387 (1950:Sep. 22). Item is in English.
- Box: 36, Folder: 6 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.296 (1948:Dec. 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.297 (1948:Dec. 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.299 (1949:Jan. 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.301 (1949:Jan. 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.302 (1949:Feb. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.303 (1949:Feb. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.304 (1949:Feb. 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.305 (1949:Feb. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.306 (1949:Mar. 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.307 (1949:Mar. 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.310 (1949:Apr. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.311 (1949:Apr. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.312 (1949:Apr. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.312 (1949:Apr. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.314 (1949:Apr. 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.315 (1949:May 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.316 (1949:May 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.317 (1949:May 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.318 (1949:May 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.319 (1949:June 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By Clothing Manufacturers Association of the U.S.A. no.320 (1949:June 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Association News Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)